A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25 FA368
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Statements and Press Releases, 9; 1 Cubic Feet
  - Power Resources, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1920)
  - Presidency, 1959-1964 (Box 91, Folder 1921)
  - Public Works, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1922)
  - Recreation, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1923)
  - Rehabilitation, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1924)
  - Republicans, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 1925)
  - Safety, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1926)
  - Social Insurance, 1959-1964 (Box 91, Folder 1927)
  - State Constitution, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 1928)
  - State Aid, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1929)
  - Transportation, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1930)
  - Veterans, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1931)
  - Waterfront, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1932)
  - Welfare, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1933)
  - World's Fair, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1934)